/ XAEll
.;„,tr7)=7.6,:sdei;;T:ir ore designed to operate it
2 Paws lass made from three mathematical equations that shot, the relation 
8) capacitor C) transformer D) .wit
h 
3 A	
occurring solid material from which a metal or valuable mineral
 A)...	
C) iron 5) lead
This is a harmful substance. Y. need to weer gloves, and if there is a risk r  
A)	
8) bolting ci welding D) splashing
5. The =moo/ panel is not working, so you cannot control the machine. It is tc  
A) inoperable B) inadequate C) incorrect D) undetected
6. Morneaury rise folbwed by a fall is called a	
A) tough 132, C) drop D) peak
7 3heomftaengerosft.i7scpiffascahore floating mobile station would be to hell
oete	
B)anchots g,lebris D) payloads
-g out what the requirements for a new project are by looking  
B., Needs analysis C) Timescale D) Budget
. , up:: cri.;77stzcestEsioyuldDliztone enter the restricted area without pe

10• A 3D model simulating shape and size, but without internal components.  
A) the acid test B) mock-up C) back-to-back testing D) full-scale test
II- The dezeal burs have to be built to last. Obviously, they need to be	
A, thermally .7..ble B) tough C) durable D) abrasion-resistant
12 Bird sznIes were a potential problem for the train 	
 to its speed.
A., =used ELL. C) because of D) owing to
13- Matta the word TRIGGER to its synonymic expresssion.  
A)44ust B)sense C) regulate D) activate
14. There is a pool of oil under the car. Something is 	
 A) leaking out  B) run out C) clogged up D) blocked up
15. I LEARNED THE HARD WAY means IT WAS	
 A, a theoretical lesson B) a practical lesson C) adequate D) what I pr
16. IT WILL BE DEAD EASY means IT WILL BE	
 A) stretching it B) borderline C) a painstaking Job D) perfectly feasit
17. An alarm sounds to prevent the boat ..... drifting unnoticed.  
A) 21 B) for C) from D) to
11. The types of connection, describing mechanical connections only, are be  
A) riveting B) welding C) fixing D) bonding
19. To remove or isolate from a circuit or networks.  
A) to resit B) to replace C) to disconnect D) to reconnect
20. T) en are two plastic ridges on either side of the plug casin,  
A oxen B) covers C) pins D) grooves	
g and they sl

